Crunchy orange carrot, fresh and sweet,
Crispy green broccoli, what a treat!
Wash your hands with soap and water clean,
Best little chef that you've ever seen!
Take a little bite, chew it slow,
Healthy foods help your body grow!
Yum, yum, munch and chew,
Good healthy food is great for you!
Fruits and veggies on my plate,
Eating yummy colors makes me feel great!
Juicy red apple, yellow banana smile,
Drink a cup of milk and rest a while!
Strawberries shining in a bowl,
Healthy snacks make our bodies whole!
Rub your happy tummy, say yum-yum,
Energy for playtime here to come!
Yum, yum, munch and chew,
Good healthy food is great for you!
Fruits and veggies on my plate,
Eating yummy colors makes me feel great!
All finished! Delicious!
Mmmm, thank you for the snack!